=Who Stole My Kiss=
= من سرق قبلتي =
=Episode 5=
= الحلقة 5 =
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm going in now.
انا ذاهب الى الداخل الآن.
Good night.
مساء الخير.
Rest early.
استرح مبكرا.
Your clothes are wet.
ملابسك مبللة.
Why not I dry it for you?
لماذا لا أجففه من أجلك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Well,
نحن سوف،
this is a homestay that my best friend is running.
هذه إقامة منزلية يديرها أعز أصدقائي.
Another friend of mine is staying here as well.
صديق آخر لي يقيم هنا أيضًا.
After all, you're a celebrity.
بعد كل شيء ، أنت من المشاهير.
I'm afraid it might cause a sensation.
أخشى أنه قد يسبب ضجة كبيرة.
Let me go in and check
اسمح لي بالدخول والتحقق
if they're here.
إذا كانوا هنا.
Okay, no problem.
حسنا لا مشكلة.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Xiaoxiao.
شياوكسياو.
He Rang.
رن.
Surprise!
مفاجئة!
Are you surprised and shocked?
هل أنت متفاجئ ومصدوم؟
Happy birthday to you!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Tingting.
تينجتينج.
He Rang insisted on giving you a birthday surprise.
أصر هو رانج على إعطائك مفاجأة عيد ميلاد.
I can't stop him.
لا أستطيع منعه.
Happy birthday to you!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Qin Mochi?
تشين موتشي؟
I'm done.
أنا انتهيت.
My image of a wise lady is all gone.
لقد اختفت صورتي عن سيدة حكيمة.
It's He Rang's bad.
إنه سيئ هو رانج.
If I stay single,
إذا بقيت عازبًا ،
I'll stay here for free.
سأبقى هنا مجانا.
Come on.
تعال.
Qin Mochi stayed
بقي تشين موتشي
to celebrate your birthday
للاحتفال بعيد ميلادك
and cooked longevity noodles for you.
وطهي المعكرونة التي تدوم طويلاً من أجلك.
It shows that he's serious.
يظهر أنه جاد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Welcome to my house.
أهلا بك في منزلي.
Thanks for
شكرا لك على
having me here.
استضافتي هنا.
(Why did you come?)
(لماذا قدمت؟)
I know you.
أنا أعرفك.
You're a celebrity.
أنت من المشاهير.
I remember that you debuted as an actor.
أتذكر أنك ترسمت كممثل.
The movie was called The Four Heroes of Peking.
الفيلم كان يسمى The Four Heroes of Peking.
You played the role of the fifth son.
لقد لعبت دور الابن الخامس.
You died in a few episodes.
لقد ماتت في بضع حلقات.
(This guy is an idiot.)
(هذا الشاب أبله.)
Yes.
نعم.
I think everyone has
أعتقد أن كل شخص لديه
their own career planning.
التخطيط الوظيفي الخاص بهم.
I prefer
أنا أفضل
the feeling on the stage,
الشعور على المسرح ،
so I chose
لذلك اخترت
to become a singer and a dancer.
لتصبح مغنية وراقصة.
I support you.
أنا أدعمك.
After all, you were not famous
بعد كل شيء ، لم تكن مشهورًا
as an actor.
كممثل.
I even advised Tingting
حتى أنني نصحت تينجتينج
not to pursue a celebrity
عدم متابعة المشاهير
that's not famous,
هذا ليس مشهورًا ،
right?
الصحيح؟
I didn't know you're so funny.
لم أكن أعلم أنك مضحك للغاية.
When are we going to eat?
متى سنأكل؟
- Right away.
- فورا.  - فورا.
Is there anything
هل يوجد أي شئ
special about the noodles?
خاص بالمعكرونة؟
The noodles are cooked with water.
يتم طهي المعكرونة بالماء.
It's worse than eating oatmeal.
إنه أسوأ من تناول دقيق الشوفان.
I've cooked your favourite...
لقد قمت بطهي طعامك المفضل ...
Maybe you don't know.
ربما لا تعرف.
When I was a trainee,
عندما كنت متدربًا ،
I ate this noodle every day.
أكلت هذه المعكرونة كل يوم.
I have yet to finish telling you what I cooked.
ما زلت لم أنتهي من إخباركم بما طهوت.
This is Yangcheng Lake's Chinese mitten crab.
هذا هو قفاز السلطعون الصيني في بحيرة Yangcheng.
The everyday training was tough.
كان التدريب اليومي صعبًا.
The company was very strict with our diet.
كانت الشركة صارمة للغاية مع نظامنا الغذائي.
So, the most expected thing
لذا ، الشيء الأكثر توقعًا
after the training
بعد التدريب
every day
كل يوم
is the noodles cooked with water.
هل المعكرونة مطبوخة بالماء.
It's simple,
انه سهل،
but
لكن
it's heartwarming.
إنه يثلج الصدر.
Thank you for being so thoughtful.
شكرا لكونك مدروس جدا
You're a man with stories.
أنت رجل لديه قصص.
My great-grandmother taught me how to make this dish.
علمتني جدتي كيف أصنع هذا الطبق.
Although...
رغم...
Tingting.
تينجتينج.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't get to
لم أتمكن من ذلك
prepare a birthday gift for you.
تحضير هدية عيد ميلاد لك.
This
هذه
is the lucky bracelet my mother made for me
هو سوار الحظ الذي صنعته أمي لي
for my debut performance.
لأدائي الأول.
I hope
آمل
you'll be as lucky as me.
ستكون محظوظا مثلي.
(It won't go wrong this time.)
(لن تسوء هذه المرة.)
I'll keep it then.
سأحتفظ به بعد ذلك.
Actually,
في الواقع،
Mochi,
موتشي ،
you can say
تستطيع أن تقول
something now.
شيء الآن.
You know what I'm going to tell you?
هل تعرف ما سأخبرك به؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you, Tingting.
شكرا لك تينجتينج.
I'm counting on you for
أنا أعتمد عليك
becoming the game ambassador.
أصبح سفير اللعبة.
The game ambassador?
سفير اللعبة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Have you forgotten?
هل نسيت؟
♪Does he like you?♪
♪ هل يحبك؟ ♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪ لا تتسرع في المقاطعة ♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪ أنت صامت ♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪ فقدت الشجاعة للحديث ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪ مطلوب
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪ احتضان أنفاسك ♪
♪Only you can♪
♪ أنت فقط تستطيع ♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪ حل اللغز اللطيف ♪
♪I like your♪
♪ أنا معجب بك ♪
♪Silly face♪
♪ وجه سخيف ♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪ فدائما ما تذكر السعادة
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪ إنها في أعماق قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت ♪
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
أمسكني بين ذراعيك ♪
♪I like♪
♪ أحب ♪
♪Being with you♪
التواجد معك ♪